Mom, would you relax? That was ten blocks from here, and the woman was walking alone
那裡離這裡有十條街 而且她是一個人在晚上走
at night. I would never do that. Mom, come on, stop worrying. This is a safe street.
This is a safe building. There's nothing... Oh, my God! What are you doing in here? Oh,
天啊！你跑進來幹什麼？
God, Mom, I gotta go. I gotta go. Okay. That's fine. You just read the paper.
沒關係，你儘管看報
I'm gonna get a pot. It's not for you. Okay, that's fine. Read the family circus. Enjoy
Oh my god! Oh my god! Oh my god! Oh my god! Oh my god! Oh my god! Oh my god! Oh my god!
Oh, god. Oh, god.
Oh, my god.
天啊！
It's open, you guys!
門是開的
Hi.
Hi. Hey, can I help you?
有何貴幹？
Yeah, I'm looking for Phoebe. Does she still live here?
菲比還住在這裡嗎？
Uh, no. She doesn't, but I can get a message to her.
沒有，但我可以幫你傳話
Great. Uh, just tell her her husband stopped by.
好，告訴她 她老公來過這裡
Her what?
她的什麼？
Hey, how did you do that?
你怎麼變出來的？
Come on.
This is unbelievable, Pheebs. How can you be married?
真是不可思議，菲比 你怎麼會結婚？
Well, I mean, I'm not married married, you know. He was just a friend, and he's gay, and he was from Canada, and he just needed a green card.
I can't believe you married Duncan. I mean, how could you not tell me? We lived together. We told each other everything.
你怎麼能不告訴我？ 我們什麼事都告訴彼此
I'm sorry, Monica, but I know if I told you, you'd get really, like, judgmental, and you would not approve.
對不起，但如果我告訴你 你會批評我…
Of course I wouldn't approve. I mean, you were totally in love with this guy, who, hello, was gay. I mean, what the hell were you thinking?
See, and you thought she'd be judgmental.
瞧？我們還以為她很愛批評
Okay, I wasn't in love with him, and I was just helping out a friend.
我並不愛他 我只是幫助一個朋友
Please, when he left town, you stayed in your pajamas for a month, and I saw you eat a cheeseburger.
他離開後你一整個月都沒下床
Well, didn't you?
有沒有？
I might have.
也許有
I can't believe you didn't tell me.
我真不相信你沒告訴我
Oh, come on, like you tell me everything?
你會告訴我一切事情嗎？
Now, what have I not told you?
我有什麼沒告訴你？
Oh, I don't know. Um, how about the fact that the underwear out there on the telephone pole is yours from when you were having sex with Fun Bobby out on the terrace?
What?
什麼？
Wait a minute. Who told you?
誰告訴你的？
You are dead meat.
你死定了
I didn't know it was a big secret.
我不知道那是個大秘密
No, it's not big.
不是大秘密 一點也不是
Not at all.
You know, kind of the same lines as, say, oh, I don't know, having a third nipple.
You have a third nipple?
你有三個乳頭？
You bitch.
你這賤人！
Whip it out, whip it out.
秀一秀！秀一秀！
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, come on. There's nothing to see. It's just a tiny bump. It's totally useless.
沒什麼好看的！ 只是個小突起，沒有用處
Oh, as opposed to your other multifunctional nipples.
你其他乳頭有多種用途羅？
I can't believe you. You told me it was a nubbin.
我真不能信任你！ 你說那是個小包
Joey, what do you think a nubbin was?
喬伊，你以為小包是什麼？
I don't know. You see something, you hear a word. I thought that's what it was.
聽到了一個名字 就不會多想了
Let me see it again.
Joey was in a porno movie.
喬伊拍過色情電影！
If I'm going down, I'm taking everybody with me.
如果我要垮台 每個人都要跟我一起垮！
All right, all right, all right, all right. I was young and I just wanted a job, okay?
But at the last minute, I couldn't go through with it.
但最後一刻我無法做下去
So they let me be the guy who comes in to fix the copier, but can't because there's people having sex on it.
他們就讓我演修影印機的人…
That is wild.
真是狂野！
So what's its shape like?
形狀是什麼樣子？ 有沒有長毛？
Is there a hair on it?
What happens if you flick it?
碰到了會怎麼樣？
So, uh, does it do anything, you know, special?
有沒有什麼特殊功能？
Why, yes, Ross. Pressing my third nipple opens the delivery entrance to the magical land of Narnia.
只要壓我的第三個乳頭…
You know, in some cultures, having a third nipple is actually a sign of virility.
在有些文化中 第三個乳頭象徵了男性雄風
You get the best huts and women dance naked around you.
有最好的住所 女人繞著你跳脫衣舞
Huh. Are any of these cultures perchance in the tri-state of California?
這些文化 是否可能在美國中部？
Tri-state area?
You know, you are so amazing. Is there anything you don't know?
你真是博學多聞 有什麼是你不知道的？
Oh, Judy's so smart. Judy's so special.
茱莉好聰明！茱莉好特別！
What, did she go and put an outfit on at night and go out and fight crime?
Look, honey, I wanted you to hook up with Ross as much as you did.
我也希望你能與羅斯復合
But he's with her now, and you're just gonna have to get over it.
但現在他與她在一起 你必須忘了他
Oh, I'm gonna have to get over it.
原來我必須忘了他
God, see, I didn't know that's what I had to do. I just have to get over it.
我不知道該怎麼辦 原來只要忘了他就好
Oh, I'm gonna have to write that down on my hand.
Where are you going?
性感美女！ 你要幹什麼？
Um, I'm gonna go meet Duncan. He's skating tonight at the garden.
我要去見鄧肯 今晚他要溜冰
He's in the capades.
他參加了冰上劇團
The ice capades? No, no, the gravel capades.
在冰上表演？ 不，在柏油路上表演
Yeah, the turns aren't as fast, but when Snoopy falls, bunny.
轉得不會很快 史努比跌倒時非常好笑
I can't believe you're dressing up for him. I mean, you're just, you're setting yourself up all over again.
Okay, no.
好的，不是
For your information, I'm going to see him so I can put all those feelings behind me.
我去看他 就是為了能徹底忘了他
Okay, and the reason I'm dressed like this is because I think it's nice to look nice for your gay husband.
我這樣打扮是因為…
Well, darn it, we're all out of milk.
該死，沒牛奶了
Hey, Chandler, would you fill me up here?
錢德，能不能給我一點？
Oh, I see, I see. Because of the third nipple thing.
我懂了，因為第三個乳頭？
Okay, sweetie, I'll see you later.
甜心，待會見
See you later, Rach.
待會見，瑞秋 再見，茱莉
Bye-bye, Julie.
Hey.
Hey, come on, cut it out.
別鬧了！
Hey.
What?
什麼？
Can I ask you something?
我能問你一件事嗎？ 好啊
Sure.
當然
Meh.
What?
什麼？
Meh.
Come on, talk to me.
對我說吧
Okay.
好的，不是
What's the longest you've been in a relationship before...
你與男人交往花了最久時間…
Having the sex.
才發生關係的是多久？
Why? Who's not having... Are you and Julie not having sex?
什麼？誰沒有…？ 你與茱莉還沒有…
Technically, no.
技術上來說？
Wow.
現在就要
Is it because she's so cold in bed?
是不是因為她很冷感？
Or is it because she's kind of bossy, makes it feel like school?
或者她非常挑剔 感覺像是在學校？
Well, no, no, she's great. And it's not like we haven't done anything.
不！她很好 我們又不是什麼都沒做
I mean, we do plenty of other stuff, lots of other stuff, like...
我們做了很多事情 像是…
No, no, no, no, don't need to know the details.
不！別告訴我細節
Okay.
好的，不是
No, it's just, it's me.
不，只是…
You know, I've only been with one woman my whole life, and she turned out to be a lesbian.
我一輩子只跟一個人上過床…
So now, I've got myself all psyched out, you know?
所以現在我很擔心
It's become like this...
就像是…
This thing, and I...
You know, you must just think I'm weird.
你一定以為我很怪
No, no, no, no, I don't think it's weird. I think...
不，我不認為很怪
I think, um, in fact, you know what I think?
你知道我怎麼想嗎？ 怎麼想？
What?
什麼？
I think it's sexy.
我覺得這很性感
Sexy?
性感？
Let me tell you something. As a woman, there is nothing sexier than a man who does not want to have sex.
No kidding?
真的？
Oh, yeah. In fact, you know what I'd do?
你知道我會怎麼做？
What?
什麼？
I'd wait.
我會等待下去
You'd wait?
Yes, absolutely. I would wait, and wait, then I'd wait some more.
Really?
真的？
Oh, yeah. I don't care how much she tells you she wants it, I don't care if she begs, she pleads,
我不管她怎麼說 她多麼想要，多麼懇求你…
she tells you she's gonna have sex with another man.
她說她要跟其他男人做愛…
That just means it's working.
這只表示收到了效果
Women really want this?
女人真的希望如此？
More than jewelry.
比珠寶還要渴望
Hi.
Phoebe!
Ta-da!
Hi.
God, look at you. You look great.
你看起來真美麗！
Do I?
Yeah.
Thank you. So do you.
Thanks.
Sparkly.
So, wow, this is pretty wonderful, huh, Mr. Major Capades Guy?
真是很棒，劇團的主角
I remember when you were just like, King Friday and Mr. Roger's Ice is Nice.
我還記得你只是 兒童節目上的道具
Yeah, you always said I'd make it.
你一直說我會成功的
Yeah, well, you know, I'm kind of spooky that way.
我總是有這方面的怪才能
I missed you.
啊，我想念你！
I'm gonna get changed.
我要換衣服 好的
Okay.
好的，不是
All right, now.
What?
什麼？
Hey.
Oh, right, okay.
喔！對，好的
Olay.
好的，不是
What?
什麼？
Um, the matador, so.
Olay.
好的，不是
Sweetie, can you hold this for a second?
甜心，你能不能拿一下？
Sure.
當然
Thanks.
Uh, Julie?
Yeah?
Sorry, you had a paleontologist on your face.
對不起，你臉上有個考古學家
But, uh, it's gone now. You're all right.
但現在沒有了，沒事
Hi, everyone.
嗨，各位
Hi.
Oh, listen, listen.
I just wanted to thank you for a little talk before.
我要謝謝你先前的指點
Oh, God, no problem.
So you're gonna go with the waiting thing?
沒問題！所以你要等下去？
Well, I was going to, but after I talked to you, I talked to Joey.
我本來要等 但是後來我又跟喬伊談了
What did he say?
很好，他怎麼說？
Basically, he told me to get over myself and just do it.
他要我去做了就對
Oh.
You know, so I thought about what you said, and I thought about what he said,
我衡量了你說的與他說的
and, well, his way I get to have sex tonight, so.
照他的話，今晚我就能做愛
Oh, God.
天啊！
What is this in my pocket?
我口袋裡有什麼東西？
Why, it's Joey's porno movie.
什麼，是喬伊的春宮電影！
Pop it in.
放出來看看！
I'm fine with it.
I mean, if you're okay watching a video filled with two-nippled people.
我不介意 只要你們願意看…
Great, people having sex.
做愛有什麼不對？
That's just what I need to see.
大家都在做愛 正是我想要看的
What's wrong with people having sex?
做愛有什麼不對？
Oh, well.
Well, um, you know, these movies are offensive and degrading to women and females.
這些電影很冒犯人…
And, uh, and the lighting's always unflattering.
燈光總是很呆板
And, Monica, help me out here.
摩妮卡，幫我一下 管你的，我要看喬伊！
Hell, I want to see Joey.
So, is there, like, a story, or do they just start doing it right?
有沒有故事？ 還是立刻就開始…
Oh.
Never mind.
別理會我
Okay, now, wait a minute.
That is the craziest typing test I've ever seen.
等一下 那是我見過最瘋狂的打字測驗
All I say is, she better get the job.
我只能說，她最好被聘用
Looks to me like he's the one getting the job.
看來是他被「聘用」了
Shh.
Okay, here I come.
我上場了
Here I come.
See, I'm coming to fix the copier.
我要修理影印機
I can't get to the copier.
I'm thinking, what do I do?
但是我修不了 我在想：怎麼辦？
What do I do?
So I just watch him have sex.
所以我只好看他們做愛
And then I say, wait, here's my line.
然後我要開口了！
You know, that's bad for the paper tray.
這對送紙匣很不好
Nice work, my friend.
幹得好，老兄！
Thank you.
真的？謝謝
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
You see me again.
你死定了
Hang on.
The guy's butt's blocking me.
等一下，又有我的鏡頭了 這傢伙屁股擋住我了
There I am.
我上場了
So, um, so what's up?
You came to see me yesterday.
怎麼回事？ 昨天你來找我
Oh, yeah, um.
All right.
嗯…
I kind of need a divorce.
我需要跟你離婚
Oh.
Okay.
好的，不是
How come?
為什麼？
Um, actually, I'm getting married again.
其實我又要結婚了
What?
什麼？
Oh, God, I don't know how to tell you this.
我不知道要怎麼說
I'm straight.
我不是同性戀
Yeah, I know.
我知道
I don't understand.
我不知道
How can you be straight?
我不懂你怎麼會是異性戀？
I mean, you're so smart and funny,
你又聰明又幽默…
and you throw such great Academy Award parties.
而且舉辦很棒的奧斯卡派對！
I know.
我知道
That's what I kept telling myself,
我也一直這麼告訴自己
but you just reach a point where you can't live a lie anymore.
但是到了某個程度 就無法再扯謊下去了
So how long have you known?
你知道了多久？
Well, I guess on some level I always knew I was straight, but...
我想我一直知道 自己不是同性戀
I thought I was supposed to be something else.
我以為自己不是
You know, I'm an ice dancer.
All my friends are gay.
I was just trying to fit in, you know?
And, um, and there's actually a woman?
真的要跟一個女人結婚？
Her name's Deborah.
她叫黛博拉
Oh.
Well, is she the first that you've been with?
她是不是你的第一個女人？
Well, I've never told you this,
我從來沒告訴過你…
but there were one or two times back in college
但在大學有一兩次…
when I'd get really drunk and go to a straight bar
我喝得大醉，去了單身酒吧
and wake up with a woman next to me.
醒來時身旁有個女人
But I told myself it was the liquor,
我以為這是因為喝酒 而且大學每個人都在摸索
and everyone experiments in college.
Sure.
當然
But now I know I don't have a choice about this.
現在我知道我沒有選擇 我生下來就是如此！
I was born this way.
I-I don't know what to say.
我不知道該說什麼
I mean, you know, you're married to someone for six years
嫁給一個人六年 以為自己很瞭解他
and you think you know him,
and then one day he says,
結果一天他說： 我不是同性戀！
Oh, I'm not gay.
I'm-I'm still me.
我還是我
Why couldn't you just have figured this out six years ago?
你為什麼在六年前 沒有發現這件事？
You know, it still smells like monkey in there.
裡面聞起來還是有猴騷味 （羅斯養過猴子）
Well, that saves us the conversation.
我們又有話可聊了
Well, listen, this has been great,
but I'm officially wiped.
今晚很好玩，但我累死了
Me, too. We should get going.
我也是，我們該走了
No!
沒有
No, I mean, no!
Come on, you guys, I mean...
不！你們別這樣！
Come on, look, it's only 11.30.
現在才十一點半
Come on, let's just talk.
We never just hang out and talk anymore.
讓我們好好聊聊 我們最近都沒有一起聊過天
Rachel, that's all we do.
瑞秋，我們在一起只有聊天
Maybe that's all we do.
What about Julie?
茱莉怎麼樣？
Well, you have been in our lives for nearly two months now,
你已經加入我們將近兩個月了
and we don't really know you.
我們還沒有真正認識你
I mean, who is Julie?
茱莉究竟是什麼樣的人？
I mean, what do you like?
What don't you like?
你喜歡什麼？不喜歡什麼？
We want to know everything.
我們什麼都要知道
That could take a while.
這可能要花一段時間
So?
所以呢？
I mean, who here does not have the time to get to know Julie?
誰沒有時間更認識茱莉？
I got the time to get to know Julie.
我有時間來認識茱莉
I got time.
我的問題
Rachel, I know her pretty well.
我跟她很熟了 我能回去嗎？
Can I go?
有何貴幹？
That's fine.
沒關係
Okay, Julie, so now let's start with your childhood.
What was that like?
茱莉怎麼樣？
Well, in a nutshell...
簡單地說…
Ah, ah, ah, ah!
So, um, have you told your parents?
你告訴了你父母嗎？
No, but it'll be okay.
還沒有，應該沒關係 他們都很酷
They're pretty cool.
My brother's straight, so...
我弟弟是異性戀，所以…
Here you go.
就是這樣了
You know, I just have one more question.
我還有一個問題
Um, if you had figured this out sooner,
如果你早一點知道 而我也在你身邊…
and, um, I had been around,
do you think that I would have been the one who...
你想會不會是我…？
No, no.
我有
That's all right, don't tell me.
我也一直這麼告訴自己
I don't think either answer would make me feel better.
我想不管什麼回答 都不會讓我更好過
So, here.
I love you, Phoebe.
我愛你，菲比
So your brother's straight, huh?
所以你弟弟是異性戀？
Seriously.
說真的
And my second-grade teacher was Miss Thomas,
我的二年級老師是湯瑪絲小姐
and my first-grade teacher was Mrs. Cobb.
我的一年級老師是柯布小姐
Mrs., Mrs. Gobb?
葛布小姐？
No, Cobb, like Cobb salad.
不，柯布，就像柯布沙拉
Now, what exactly is in a Cobb salad?
柯布沙拉裡面究竟有什麼？
I'm going home.
我要回家了
Well, that Julie's a talker, huh?
茱莉真是愛說話，嗯？
Good night.
晚安
So, it's pretty late.
You're probably not still planning on...
很晚了，你們大概沒有打算…
Oh, no, no, I am.
Oh.
Hey, are you nervous?
你緊張嗎？
No, no, I, uh...
I have done it before.
我以前做過
Okay, I mean, how are you gonna handle it?
你要如何進行？
I mean, are you gonna...
Are you gonna talk about it beforehand?
要先談談？還是就上了？
Are you just gonna pounce?
I mean, I don't know.
我不知道
I guess I'm just gonna see what happens, you know?
Okay, good luck.
祝你好運！
Well, uh...
What?
什麼？
Nothing.
沒事…
I mean, um, it is your first time with her,
and, you know, if the first time doesn't go well,
這是你與她的第一次 如果第一次就不順利…
well, then that's pretty darn hard to recover from.
那就很難再東山再起
Okay, now I'm nervous.
好，現在我緊張了
Maybe you should put it off.
也許你應該延期
No, no, I don't want to put it off.
不，我不要延期！
I...
喔…
God, I'm just...
不，只是…
I spent last year being so unbelievably miserable,
我去年一整年都很悲慘
and now, now I'm actually happy.
現在我很快樂
You know, I mean, really happy.
真的很快樂
I just, I just don't want to...
我不希望…
I don't want to mess it up, you know?
我不希望搞砸了，你知道吧？
I know.
我知道
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
對不起
No, it's...
不，只是…
It's not your fault.
這又不是你的錯
Right.
嗯…
Maybe it doesn't have to be this tough.
也許不需要這麼困難
I mean, maybe you were on the right track
你要如何進行？
with that whole, you know, spontaneous thing.
I mean, women really like that.
女人真的喜歡這樣 真的？
Really?
真的？
Yeah.
I mean, you know, I mean, if it were me,
I'd, you know, I'd want you to...
如果是我，我會希望你…
What?
什麼？
I don't know, catch me off guard, you know,
趁我沒有防備的時候…
with, like, a really good kiss.
You know, really sort of, um, soft at first.
剛開始要很輕柔
And then maybe, um, brush the hair away from my face.
然後也許把我的頭髮撥開
Uh-huh.
And then look far into my eyes
凝視我的眼睛…
in a way that lets me know something
讓我知道有美妙的事情…
amazing is about to happen.
快要發生了
Uh-huh.
And then, I don't know,
然後，我不知道，然後…
then you'd pull me really close to you
你會更緊地摟住我…
so that I'd be pressed up, you know, right against you.
我會緊緊帖著你…
And, um, it would get kind of...
然後就會開始…
sweaty.
流汗…
And, uh, and blurry.
目眩神迷…
And then it's just happening.
一切就自然發生…
Oh.
Thanks, man. Good night.
謝謝，瑞秋，晚安！
Oh!
天啊！
Oh, God.
I'm singing in the rain
Yes, singing in the rain
What a glorious feeling I'm having
Good morning.
早安！
Well, somebody got some last night.
昨晚有人爽到了！
Twice.
兩次！
Yes.
Singing in the rain